As countries worldwide are battling
a discrete yet fierce information war,
Westalis launched "Operation Strix,"
in order to track the movements
of Ostania's key government officials.
B-1 Agent, Twilight,
is in charge of the operation.
He successfully completed Phase One,
by creating a family
and enrolling his daughter into
a prestigious school.
Currently, she managed to secure one of
the eight Stella Stars
that are necessary to become
an honor student.
The mission has now entered Phase Two,
which is to attend the reception where
the target, Desmond, will appear.
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
MISSION 20:
INVESTIGATE THE GENERAL HOSPITAL
The social studies project this time,
is to research an occupation
that interests you.
You may ask your parents
about their workplace
or interview local shops and companies.
You may also have your parents arrange
an interview with prominent figures.
And of course, if you want to do research
about teachers, you may come to me.
I will lecture you on
the pride of an educator.
Prepare a report about your research
and present it to the class on Friday.
Damian, will you interview your father?
If I can reach him.
I'll get this done efficiently
by asking my dad about his company.
What about you, Anya?
Job research?
We were told to ask
why you chose the job,
and how we can work in that field.
And they told us to observe you at work.
What? My job?
What should I do?
She wants to observe me at work?
But which job?
Are you ready, Anya?
Let me tell you about my job.
Okay.
I first started this job
in order to support my younger brother,
but now I take pride in my work.
Shopkeeper also told me
that this is a noble calling,
and I'm like a soldier
who devotes her life to her homeland.
Oh, it's a mission from the Shopkeeper.
This is my target.
He's a bastard traitor!
It seems like he's done horrible things
that I can't even mention to you, Anya.
Let's go see him.
-Can you keep up with me, Anya?
-Yes.
The Shop researches the target's
capabilities and layout of the security,
so I just have to get inside.
I must kill the enemy at first sight,
but killing the wrong person
is out of the question,
so I make sure to read the file carefully.
I approach boldly,
since I have nothing to be ashamed of.
There's danger!
This job is rewarding
because I know that I am
cleaning up this country.
When I think of all the lives that are
being protected because of my job,
it instills power into my weapon.
What this job requires is
training of the body and technique.
A good understanding of
human anatomy is helpful too.
The enemy is a human after all,
so I strive to kill them
quickly without causing too much pain.
For example, if you take
the knife on the neck, and cut it,
a human will die instantly.
Aside from that, a precise hit to
the vital parts of the brain and heart…
Oh no, are you okay, Anya? Let's tell Loid
that we went to the tomato festival!
Anya is thinking of doing research
on Father's job.
Is that right?
That sounds like a good idea!
A job at the City Hall is meaningful,
but it might be a little boring for you.
I'm back.
Father, this and that.
Okay. Roger.
TWO DAYS LATER
BERLINT GENERAL HOSPITAL
I work in the Psychiatric Department
of this hospital.
Everyone knows you're coming today,
but don't cause any trouble.
Okay.
It's huge.
It's the most prominent hospital
in the capital.
Being a private medical practitioner
would've been a better cover,
but key figures in the political, business
and military circles use this hospital.
So I can steal intel,
and it gives me the opportunity
to forge connections.
I haven't said anything for you
to take notes on.
And what's with that outfit?
-It's the classic investigation outfit.
-I see.
Psychiatrists don't usually
wear lab coats,
but this makes me look more
like a doctor, right?
What are you going to research?
The first question is,
why did you choose this job?
The reason why I chose this job?
Let's see.
Everyone catches a cold
and gets sick, right?
Sometimes your mind gets sick too.
There are many people in this world
whose mind catches a cold.
The second son told me that I'll never
catch a cold because I'm dumb.
I see. Try to get along with him.
Anyways,
I wanted to help those people out.
There are also many veterans
who are still suffering
even years after the war ended.
I figured that if Desmond
is secluding himself from society
because of some sickness,
then I could perhaps approach him
as a doctor…
I made a firm resolve in college…
The next question is,
what's the work atmosphere like?
Atmosphere?
Hello, Doctor Forger.
Is this your daughter?
These are my colleagues. Say hello.
It's very nice to meet you.
You're so cute!
What a good girl, doing your homework!
She's so cute like a princess.
Here's a snack for you.
Father's workplace is like paradise.
Good for you.
How is my father at work?
He's so cool!
He's so attentive and kind
towards the patients too.
Your father is an amazing man.
He quickly became our leading force
soon after he transferred here.
But he's not arrogant,
and is loved by everyone.
By the way, my friend
in the Neurology Department said that
she wants Doctor Forger to attend
the next gathering…
The Director wants to go golfing with you.
Father, are you popular?
Well, I try to be sociable.
Can you tell the Director…
It's best to widen my network.
It makes it easier to gain intel
and connections, but most importantly,
a spy must make others think,
"No, there's no way he's a spy."
One must be sociable without standing out.
You keep on writing notes at weird times.
What's the most difficult part
about this job?
That's a good question.
Let's see.
It's the difficulty of working with
the mind, which is not visible.
Doctors aren't wizards.
We can't read people's minds.
Why do you look so proud?
Because we can't read minds,
we must let go of all preconceptions,
and observe carefully and patiently,
and interact with them.
It's just like a spy
getting to know his target.
But one big difference is
a spy would betray that trust in the end…
These snacks are so good.
Do you want some more?
-Do you want juice?
-Want to take a personality test?
I'm done answering questions.
Father is so serious.
That's his charm.
We wish you would use your talent
and work at the clinic.
I'm sorry.
I'm so busy with my research studies.
I guess what's most difficult,
is the fact that I'm doing this
along with my mission.
All right, we'll head back to work.
Bye Anya!
I was to see you actually working.
The consultations?
I can't let you do that since it concerns
the patient's privacy.
I can't let outsiders
near my research either.
I guess I can let you see
the consultation room.
I don't plan to use this room today.
This is not like the operation room.
It looks like a normal room.
It's made this way to help
the patients relax.
Where's the brain reconstruction machine?
What do you think psychiatrists do?
Stop fooling around
and let's finish all of your questions.
What kind of anime is she
getting this from?
I'm pretty much finished now.
I'm a little bored now.
Don't touch anything!
Create a ruckus and I'll get mad.
Behind this bookshelf,
is an emergency escape route
for my missions.
It will move once the lever is pulled.
A hidden passage! Lever!
Oh, it's a WISE agent.
Sorry, some urgent business came up.
Since you're finished,
should I have Yor come pick you up?
I'll wait until your work is finished.
Being a spy is hard work.
Okay.
Then play with this while you wait.
I use these during consultations.
Arrange these figurines and other items
however you like inside this box.
It'll be fun.
Sounds boring.
Listen up. Don't touch anything else.
Okay.
I'll be back in ten minutes.
Huh.
The materials for
the revised version of the DSM.
-They should arrive by this weekend.
-Thanks.
In order to keep my cover,
there are few agents working
within this hospital.
Another mission, huh.
-Did you work out my schedule here?
-Of course.
That child I saw earlier is Anya Forger?
She seems to be close to you.
She's unpredictable so it keeps me
on my toes.
I'm surprised that she's able to
challenge you.
What an exciting adventure!
The hidden passage is so narrow.
Today's topic is about
paranormal experience and neuroscience.
Is it a serious meeting?
Of all the reported cases,
five percent are unexplainable…
This is absurd!
Those who talk about seeing ghosts
and what-not are mythomaniacs!
Or it could be illusions caused by
abnormal cerebral dysfunction.
There is no scientific proof.
Ghost stories? How exciting!
Did you hear something?
But there are no rooms above us.
Oh no! They'll find out about
the hidden passage.
You're just hearing things.
Anyway, if this topic comes up
when providing treatment,
we must be very careful--
It's a waste of time to even discuss it.
Let's end this meeting.
Anya has to go back soon,
or Father will return!
My foot is stuck, and I can't get it out!
Anya is in a crisis!
What is that? There's something up there!
It sounds like a baby's cry!
It's a ghost! It's got to be a ghost!
I got it out! I have to hurry back!
It went away.
I heard about a baby who haunts this
place because it died due to malpractice.
It was a true story!
Everyone, let's continue our meeting!
Yes, let's! From now on,
we must listen to clients
who speak about paranormal activities.
Let's see how she arranged everything
inside that box.
Father is coming back!
I have to hurry up and make something!
I'm back.
Playing with these figurines
is so much fun.
Let's take a look. Believe it or not,
this game reveals a bit of
a person's unconscious mind.
Let's see what's on your mind.
It's chaos!
What is this?
I've never seen a case like this!
I just threw everything in.
What's up with these figurines
that are scattered and buried?
They were all attacked
by the bad people's rolling sweep attack.
What is this?
I don't know what this means,
but it's a catastrophe!
I was so preoccupied
that I failed to realize
that she was taken from
the orphanage to live with a stranger.
It's normal for her to experience stress.
No, Father, this is…
She must have been trying so hard
to suppress and hide her feelings.
I never knew that it had evolved into
this deep, dark abyss.
No, I was just pretending not to see it.
Yes, this is my weakness.
I have failed as a spy.
I must help her.
Let's go home for today.
Let's buy the latest Spy Wars book
at the bookstore.
Y… yay!
Let's write up the report together
after dinner.
-Did you take lots of notes?
-No, Father…
My notes about the spy…
What is this?!
I can't read her writing at all.
Um… this is…
Anya will work hard
and write the report on her own.
Is that right? Good girl! You're the best!
Mother, we're home!
Welcome home!
Were you able to see Loid's
super cool concussive therapy?
Concussive?
Um, Yor, that's only used
during emergencies.
He was throwing down patients
left and right.
It was a sight to see.
Father is violent.
Yor…
In the future,
I hope I can do the same kind of job.
The end.
That was a very heartfelt,
and elegant report.
Next is Anya Forger.
Father's job is a sp…
spectacular doctor who heals the mind.
In order to provide the patients
with peace of mind,
he works hard while sacrificing sleep
and taking digestive medicine.
He said he wants to help people
who faced hardships during the war.
How lovely!
Just as I expected, Loid Forger.
In order to build trust with his targets,
he communicates with them
carefully and patiently.
Target?
Father is frantically trying to
make connections.
During work, he plays golf
and has hidden secrets in his room.
He's also passing out snacks.
Snacks? Is that some code for bribery?
Also, he apparently punches
his patients sometimes.
Loid Forger…
What's wrong, Twilight?
Nothing, I just got the chills.
Later on, Loid was summoned to school,
but he was able to evade trouble
with his super eloquent skills.
Top secret. A secret mission, huh?
A cipher?
SECRET CODE
Saturday. 8 a.m.
Meet me on the bridge.
MISSION 20: DECIPHER THE ARCANE CIPHERS
No wonder you're an elite member
of the organization.
You deciphered that so easily.
Anya's going to write a cipher too.
She's playing spy, huh.
-Anya.
-This is top secret!
Deciphering your code will be
the least of your problems.
Her writing
is impossible to read
even with my deciphering skills.
Oh no.
I'm off to my night shift.
Make sure you study.
I love this scent of soap.
Mother, I have a favor to ask.
What is it, Anya?
Can you write down something for me?
SECRET CODE
The cipher is complete.
Listen up. This is a secret mission.
It's top secret.
Here's your mail.
Miss.
Put a stamp on the letter
and take it to the post office.
Oh no.
He rejected my cipher.
You can't do that, Anya.
-Right?
-That's so true.
Oh my. What is this?
What a strange letter. Is it a prank?
Come to think of it, my son was writing
something similar to this.
He was copying some spy anime.
Oh, is that what it is?
That child is always pretending
to be a spy, isn't she?
Hey, what are you doing here?
-Scruffy.
-Is Loid home?
What? He's not home?
Fine then. I'll come back later.
Huh?
What is this? A message from Loid?
Tsk, tsk. It's top secret.
Good morning, Anya.
What is this? A letter?
It's not?
I got it.
It's the quiz that's popular these days!
It's top secret.
Come on Anya, tell me what it is!
Stop being mysterious
and tell me the answer!
Top secret!
Huh? What is this?
It's a cipher. Try to decipher it.
Why do I have to decipher this?
Do it yourself!
I'm excited to see who will come tomorrow!
You're amazing after all.
You were able to decipher that code.
Oh, this is the thing from yesterday.
What was this supposed to be?
It looks like a cipher.
This soft handwriting…
Was this written by a woman?
It smells good like soap!
Could this be a love letter?!
Can you give this to him?
Keep it a secret.
This love is a top secret.
Saturday. 8 a.m.
Meet me on the bridge.
Don't underestimate the top informant
of the east and west.
Deciphering a simple code
is child's play to me!
But I was so excited that I couldn't
sleep a wink last night!
The morning sun is so bright!
She used a secret code to meet me.
Where is this agent from?
Or is she a mystery lover?
"Decipher this love code
and come find me."
Is that what it means?
It's top secret.
MISSION 21: NIGHTFALL
JEALOUSY FOR THE FIRST TIME
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita